{
    "id": "20f929751f8a4c7d907c5b8cc9a543f6",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The minister spoke of the soul’s …………………………. life.",
            "description": "Eternal means lasting forever.",
            "answers": [
                "eternal",
                "ethereal"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ………………………………. beauty could not be captured by the greatest painter.",
            "description": "Ethereal means celestial.",
            "answers": [
                "eternal",
                "ethereal"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ……………………………….. would not allow her to betray a friend.",
            "description": "Ethics means moral code.",
            "answers": [
                "ethics",
                "ethnics"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Each country has its own ……………………………… costumes.",
            "description": "Ethnic means cultural or native.",
            "answers": [
                "ethic",
                "ethnic"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The politician’s …………………………….. answers infuriated the reporters.",
            "description": "Evasive means elusive or misleading.",
            "answers": [
                "evasive",
                "allusive",
                "invasive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The procedure was only minimally …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "evasive",
                "invasive",
                "elusive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "An …………………………… spends much time alone.",
            "description": "Introvert means private person.",
            "answers": [
                "introvert",
                "introspective",
                "intravert"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………………………………… sense of humor helped him through hard times.",
            "description": "Invincible means unconquerable.",
            "answers": [
                "invisible",
                "invincible",
                "invinsible"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. romantics are always falling in love.",
            "description": "Inveterate means steadfast, diehard.",
            "answers": [
                "incorrigible",
                "die-hard",
                "inveterate",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "In an ……………………………. position, a 9 looks like a",
            "description": "Inverted means upside down.",
            "answers": [
                "converted",
                "inverted",
                "perverted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The sinner ……………………………….. the Lord’s forgiveness.",
            "description": "Invoke means call upon.",
            "answers": [
                "invoked",
                "evoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}